smartshanghai.com 2013-06-30

# SmartShanghai.com | Privacy Policy

SmartShanghai.com Privacy Policy

This is a privacy policy for SmartShanghai.com.

SmartShanghai respects your privacy and safeguarding your privacy is very important to us.  
Below is an outline of the information that SmartShanghai.com gathers and how it's used.

Whenever you request a page through your browser, navigation and clickstream data such as: 

  * your IP address,
  * browser and version,
  * operating system,
  * date and time and
  * the site from which you came

are stored in a log file and/or database. This information cannot be used to identify specific individuals, and is only used for: 

  * Website and system administration,
  * research and development,
  * anonymous user analysis, and to provide accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data. 

SmartShanghai uses **cookies** to enable site features including, but not limited to login data, time and date tracking. We recommend that you browse SmartShanghai with cookies enabled in your browser. Our advertising partners may use cookies as part of their advertising campaign but this is independent of this site.

The email addresses collected from subscriptions to the SmartShanghai **newsletters** are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used by our business to send out SmartShanghai communications (for example "Shanghai_nightlife"). According to the terms of subscription, SmartShanghai.com may send a maximum of one advertisement e-mail per month which will clearly be labelled as a publication sent out by SmartShanghai.com. You will not receive any mailings you did not request. The email addresses collected at SmartShanghai.com are stored on a server hosted by Computer Solutions in Shanghai, P.R. China. 

Any email sent from SmartShanghai.com contains a direct unsubscribe link at the bottom which allows subscribers and site-members to unsubscribe directly.

SmartShanghai does not display pictures or personal information of it's **dating** members to non-members. Dating profiles are available to other users of the website and can also be accessed by authorized personnel. Dating members can remove their pictures or the entire dating profile on their own. Search engines have no access to SmartShanghai dating pages. 

SmartShanghai gives all registered **users** the options for deleting their profile and by that removing any personal information previously provided.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policies, or require assistance in opting out of our email lists, please contact us using our [contact form here](http://www.smartshanghai.com/contact).

SmartShanghai.com, Dec 2010
